https://interfusellc.com/privacy-policy/

Products
Ball BearingsBalloonsCake ToppersCar LCDsCar LEDsCar Ribbon CablesHDMI CablesLED FlashlightsMining LightsScreen ProtectorsUSB AdaptersUSB Cables
ELM327
ELM327 AccessoriesELM327 BluetoothELM327 DriversELM327 InterfaceELM327 ManualsELM327 MiniELM327 SoftwareELM327 USBELM327 Wifi
OBD2 Scanners
CablesCode ReadersDiagnostic ToolsProgrammersTrouble Codes
Madison Liquidators
BookcasesChairsConference TablesCubiclesDesksFiling Cabinets
Spudgers
Metal SpudgersNylon SpudgersPlastic SpudgersSpudger KitsSpudger Tool Sets
Sites We Maintain
Information WorksGame Tips GuideGreene-Niesen InsuranceLinkTo.DirectoryMadison LiquidatorsNick NiesenOBD2 ScannerSpudgers.comTopsitenet.comUberant.com
Support
About UsContact UsKnowledgebaseLoginNews & UpdatesPress ReleasesPrivacy PolicyRegisterReturnsShippingSites We Maintain
privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for (Interfuse LLC.). This
privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It
will notify you of the following:
What
personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web
site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What
choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The
security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How
you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and
Sharing
We
are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have
access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other
direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We
will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted
us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our
organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. give a
quote or answer questions about an item.
Unless
you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about
specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over
Information
You
may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the
following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number
given on our website:
•
See what data we have about you, if any.
• Change/correct any data we have about you.
• Have us delete any data we have about you.
• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We
take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive
information via the website, your information is protected both online and
offline.
Wherever
we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information
is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by
looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking
for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While
we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also
protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to
perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted
access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which
we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Updates
Our
Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on
this page.
If
you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us
immediately via telephone at (833) 404-0001 or via e-mail at support@interfusellc.com.
© 2020 Interfuse LLC. All Rights Reserved.
